if you are a course creator or coach the
very best lead Manet that you can create
is the one that produces the most sales
for you now let me explain the best
types of lead magnets in this video I'm
going to be walking you through the
different types there are and why
there's one type that I think is better
than all the rest that you should be
doing in your own business by the way
it's not challenges it's not webinars
it's not what you think it is it's
actually something very new very unique
that we're using right now in our
business that is going to get you a lot
of sales and a lot of clients for those
of you that I haven't met yet my name is
Jeremiah Kowski for the last 21 years
it's almost 22 years now I have been in
the online marketing and coaching space
building businesses to tens of millions
of dollars I personally built multiple
coaching businesses over the $10 million
year mark and I've helped thousands of
clients scale their businesses to six
and even seven figures and so if you
want to know what's the best way to do
so I got to tell you you got to grow
your email list that's the number one
thing people who don't have an email
list they don't have clients they don't
have people that are buying from them
and without people on your email list
you don't have people that you can
Market to you might say well there's
people on social media I could do
Instagram reals I could do all this
again those are ways to get people onto
your email list so I want you to write
that down all the different channels of
marketing that we see whether it be
affiliate marketing podcasting SEO
blogging Instagram reels uh YouTube like
this it's all about getting people onto
your email list and then by taking those
people that are on your email list
because 100% of your clients are going
to first be on your email list and you
want to create a system to where nobody
gets offered you don't try to sell
anything until somebody is on your email
list in our business that's exactly what
we've done to scale our business this
one that I have right now to over seven
figures that's what we've done to build
multiple coaching businesses over eight
figures is by promoting some kind of a
lead magnet something that grows the
email list so here's why
because for people to spend money with
you $1,000 $2,000
$10,000
$36,000 have a client right now that
sells a $36,000 program he also has a
$155,000 program and he sells a lot of
them every single one of those people
comes from his email list first and
there's not a single person who can
interact with him without first getting
on the email list sure he's got
Instagram reals and stuff like that but
he ends up then leading people to join
his email list and so that's the number
one thing that you got to got to make
sure of is that you are building a list
of people that you can Market
to and you might say well email is dead
I don't open all my emails well here's
the
thing is that if you're emailing your
list consistently and and consistently
means at least once a
day I I mean a lot of coaches like yeah
I don't want to buy bug people I don't
want to bother people can I tell you
something straight up I'm going to give
you some coaching and and maybe you're
not going to like what I'm about to say
your fear of bugging
people is why you're not making the kind
of money that you want to make the worry
of irritating and annoying people is why
your business is not making the kind of
money that you want to make when you can
get past that you will be able to print
more money than the Federal government
does I didn't come up with that one that
was actually something I got from a guy
uh uh Scott uh old old Ford or I think
that's his name anyways it was great but
it's true if you can get used to
irritating people enough you don't it's
not it's not that you're trying to
irritate them but you don't worry about
it you do things without fear of
irritating other people you just do the
thing you can make so much money
because you're consistently promoting
what you have to offer you're
consistently telling people about the
thing that you have to offer in my
business I have a coaching program
called the client growth accelerator
program where I work with you to build
your lead magnet create your ads dial in
your messaging and sell more in your
business if you're a coach Mentor course
creator I'd love to see you inside of my
accelerator program you can click the
link in the description of this video to
find more info about that
now by the way some of you the fact that
I just said that might be irritated that
I did a little mini commercial in the
middle of this video can I tell you
something that's why I make more money
than you do and that's why my clients
make more money because we are not
afraid to promote and Market what we
have to offer on every piece of content
that we have and so growing past that
internal work and fear and again you
might need to talk with a therapist
about
that I'm not joking cuz I did and I had
to work through some mental issues as to
why I was so terrified of annoying other
people as honestly because growing up I
thought I was an annoyance to everybody
around me if you can grow past this you
can make a ton of money and then start
promoting your lead magnet to people
they might be saying well what kind of
lead magnet should I have I don't know
my Niche I don't know my topic I don't
know what to do well that's where AI can
be very very helpful as well using
YouTube and YouTube is one of my
favorite resources for figuring out what
topic to create for your lead magnet but
let's not skip ahead here okay the
different types of lead magnets that you
can create are as
follows the very simplest is going to be
an
ebook right here ebook
simple um you know we created one of
these for a client of mine right here
help them Market at at thousands of
leads free AI stocks book it's a it's a
book it's an ebook so you go in you can
type in your name and I'm going to show
you this right here free download boom
grab the download that's a lead magnet
that leads to a 20 it's a 26 page ebook
we used AI even to help us put it
together it was based on a lot of
different teachings that we had already
taught on video to promote a stock
market market trading program called the
stocks group right here okay so that's
this program right here the program is
177 bucks a month or you can get an
incredible deal by getting it for 12
months for
$693 amazing okay so all that to say
ebook is a great way to promote an offer
like that another way to do it is you
can have a video class okay this could
be a pre-recorded class I have one I'm
about to Launch right now I'm going to
show you this um honestly it's not even
like ready to launch yet but I'm going
to show you what this looks like so we
have
a let's pull this up on my site
here this it's a free class uh get more
coaching clients with Facebook ads right
here okay I talk about what I'm going to
teach you got some client testimonials
on there people can sign up for it I
thank them for joining they check their
email and and then boom right here watch
the training it's a it's a class that I
did right here all on Facebook ads okay
and so but I'm requiring people to sign
up with their email address so that I
can either promote it through Instagram
reels I can run ads to it and I can get
people on my email list to
then start to promote my business which
is my accelerator program in every piece
of content that I have I'm mentioning my
accelerator program
now is everybody who wops in everybody
who joins my email list are they all
going to become clients no they're not
in fact it's actually less than 5% that
do for me it's closer to 10% but for
most people it's between 3 to
5% and so not everybody is going to sign
up or become a client of yours but what
you're doing is is you're looking to
find the gold the people that
will that's a select group of people
it's not every body that are going to
become a client of yours by offering
something of value whether it be in the
form of an ebook the form of a video
class you could also do it in the form
of a live event by the way these are
also some of my favorite ways of doing
this we we got a ton of clients back in
June I did a live event right here
called create and launch your sixf
figure group coaching Community offer
without burnout it was a 2hour live
training that I taught live on June 5th
it's a very specific specific date and
time you had to show up at that time I
think you had just a couple of days to
grab the
recording and we got a lot of clients
off of that and so these are like my
three favorite versions of lead magnets
but the very best one that I'm going to
say that you're going to that that I
think people are looking for now is
something that is
under 40
minutes and honestly you if you can go
under 30 minutes that's even better
the shorter the better but you want to
make sure that you can at least cover
everything like there's a lot of stuff
to cover sometimes in these lead magnets
that we have but if you have a piece of
video
content that people can give you their
email address for and then you deliver
that content and at the same time you're
able to present them with an
irresistible offer to become a client of
yours you know this could look like
offering them a free trial to your
program this could offer a discount
bonuses that might expire you could have
a deadline there's a tool called
deadline funnel that we like to do you
know give people 3 to 5 days to make a
decision to join based on that have some
autoresponder emails going out these
automatic emails reminding people to
watch the video content that they signed
up for to sign up for the program and so
that is what we're finding right now to
be the very best kind of lead magnet the
other way that we like to do it is that
you can use Instagram reels have people
leave a comment and use a tool called
many chat so we love using many chat
because what you can do is you can send
somebody a link to something by them
commenting on the video let me show you
what this looks like here's a client of
mine right here we're working with with
an A Min chat campaign he has this video
right here comment the word YouTube and
I will send you this video so look it
he's sitting in his backyard super chill
but he got all these comments people
YouTube YouTube YouTube and then when
you do that it sends them a YouTube
video and that YouTube video alone I'm
going to tell you
this has made him a ton of money I don't
want to say how much it is but it's it's
multi6 Figures it's a lot of
money um off of that one video off of
that one instagram re right there by
sending people they comment it and then
it sends a direct message in the inbox
looks kind of like this hey here's the
training right here you click on get
updates it sends them to the YouTube
video okay and so right there is a great
way for you to get connected with
people send them a piece of content some
video that's under 40 minutes long under
30 minutes long and then that's where
you can present what your offer is now
you want to provide value like this
watch this video right here is a bit of
what you would offer if you watch any of
my YouTube videos by the way they really
fit into this framework that we're
talking about here we deliver value
every YouTube video that I have is
highly valuable I have my paid clients
watch my YouTube videos because they're
so valuable they they love them but I'm
delivering these for free it's free
value that I'm giving away it's free
information that I'm sharing that you
can learn from that you can apply that
you can get results from in your
business but since you didn't pay for it
it's going to be sponsored by I'm not
going to say sponsored by but it's going
to be sponsored by what I have to offer
and so for the exchange of me giving you
this free information there's an
unspoken contract there I think that
people agree to that okay I don't mind
if you sell me a little bit on what your
thing is that you offer now again I have
met people they get tired of it I don't
want to be pitched
something like I meet people they're
like I just don't want to be pitch
something I'm just
like great
I'm in a business you came here for
business
information I don't mean to be cocky
here but there are some people they just
have a version in their mind of business
that doesn't involve
sales and it's not reasonable realistic
or built on reality at all it's built on
this idea that like you make good
content and then people will contact you
if they want to work with
you the problem is I tried that for
years back in 2018 and nobody reached
out to me to want to become a
client and I thought that I was doing
all the right things just by putting
value out there and not actually having
any call to action because I didn't want
to irritate or offend or upset anybody
as soon as I started promoting offers
telling people I had something for sale
having lead magnets growing my email
list the number one thing that has grown
my business and all my clients's
businesses is growing the email list
requiring people to get give you their
info their email contact
info business is grown and so listen if
you're a coach or course creator
creating some kind of a lead magnet some
piece of value that you offer and in
exchange you also mention the thing that
you have for sale and there's a
different degree of mentioning if you're
requiring them to give you your email
your the email address you can have a
much more in-depth sales pitch to it if
it's just a YouTube video like this you
might notice my YouTube videos I don't
pitch a lot on these YouTube videos I
mentioned I got a got an amazing
coaching program for sale every single
one of you absolutely needs to be in
there because it's the best it's amazing
it's incredible our clients love it
but I'm not using this as the way of
pitching but what I will say is click
the link in the description and I'd love
for you to check out our program and
what we have to offer get on our waiting
list or when we by the way we change the
link that's below this video all the
time so you might see an offer below
there you might see a free class you
might see uh something like that so just
check out what we have in the
description and get into our ecosystem
join my email list see the emails that I
send out see what emails that I'm
marketing you can literally look at the
emails that I send out and use that as a
model for you for how to Market and sell
in your own business
okay now how do we come up with what
topic to create for our offers number
number one you want to listen to your
Market what do people actually want what
are their desires okay people aren't
going to give you their email address
for something that you want to give them
I can tell you this um the only reason
anybody gives me their email address I
have a lot of stuff that I love teaching
people I have a wide range of topics
that I that I I share with people but
not every
topic is a good
idea to make a lead magnet around
because oftentimes it might be a great
topic that's going to provide a ton of
value to people and yet crickets nobody
signs up for it and here's why because
you have to also be effective at how you
present the offer you got to package it
in a way when I say packaging it's not
about how the camera looks or the
lighting or anything like that the
packaging has to do with the words that
you're using to describe it the
messaging what is the hook how do you
describe the promised outcome that
they're going to get from that offer so
like when I when I show you this right
here um create and launch your sixf
figure group coaching Community this one
right here uh get more coaching clients
with Facebook ads I mean those are
actually pretty
good those are actually like they're
very specific outcom driven
they're they're very lasered in as far
as the as far as what people want to
learn from
me whereas if it was just like I'm going
to show you how to get more coaching
clients by the way I've tested that out
I get almost nobody who signs up but as
soon as I add that little piece to it
with Facebook
ads tons of people want to sign up that
all want to know how to do Facebook ads
and a lot of what we do has to do with
Facebook ads we take the Instagram reals
format we promote those videos through
Facebook and Instagram and Tik Tok we
get people to our lead magnets and
that's how we present to people we end
up presenting to the people that come in
through our lead magnets okay so again
one of the best ways to find topics that
you can do number one is listening to
your audience once you connect with
people listening to what they want what
they care about you can do this again in
your Instagram you can do this on your
social media by creating a community of
people around you
that
are in the niche and by the way Niche
has to do with a type of person not a
topic not a thing a niche is who not
what so who is the type of person that
you serve what is the outcome that you
deliver to them and how do you help them
get a result and then from there you can
reverse engineer that back into an idea
for an offer so couple ways that we do
this you can either use chat GPT to do
it this is totally free let's say I help
dog walkers grow their business
brainstorm 20 lead magnet ideas that I
could create as a video lead magnet you
could also create a checklist that's
another form of a lead magnet right here
I didn't write that one down yet is the
checklist that then leads to a video so
it's like it's like here I'm going to
give you this free download
checklist um and then after it it's a
video that basically breaks down the
topic like you break down all the points
from the checklist and you have some
kind of a Next Step that you want them
to take inside of every lead magnet that
you want to
have all of your lead magnets need to
have some kind of a next step I meet a
lot of people they create a lead magnet
and there's no next step they're just
like well I hope you like that
content I hope you enjoyed
that I'm like and so how do you expect
to get sales well they're going to you
know they're going to go to my website
and they're going to write me and
they're going to say I want to work with
you that's not reality human beings do
not operate that way in business so you
got to lead people to whatever the next
step is that you want them to take
whether it be
getting on a waiting list list whether
it be joining you at another event
whether it be subscribing to your email
list whether it be and by the way if
they're already on your email list
getting them to sub subscribe to your
email list for another offer that's okay
because that single activity of getting
people to take action to sign up for
something again even after they've
already subscribed it's a great thing
because psychologically it triggers
something in their mind where they're
like oh okay I took action here here but
then I took action over here and they
get looped in and it reinforces in the
neurotransmitters in their brain it's
literally a brain wiring thing it wires
their brain to say that they're more
committed because they sign up for a
second thing with you so I madean a lot
of people they'll have like a free offer
and I say listen just give them another
offer at the end of it another thing a
Next Step that you want them to take of
some
kind and so that's going to reinforce
that and even if they don't take you up
on it even just the activity of them
looking at it will reinforce that in
their mind to pay attention to you next
time they see you on the social media
okay so again AI you can do this I help
dog walkers grow their business five
tips to keeping your dog walk your dog
calm during walks Ultimate Guide to
choosing the right leash and color for
your dog how to train your
dog um let
see I want to gear the so you'll notice
these were not actually good ideas for
these Le
magnets so I stopped it and I said I
want to gear these towards business
owners who have businesses that walk
dogs and do dog grooming
okay here's 20 ideas for that how to
attract more clients your dog rooming
business guide to pricing your dog gring
services top five tools every dog
walking business needs how to build a
loyal client base in your dog groom
business uh building creating a
memorable brand okay
generate 20 YouTube video ideas based on
the above so now this is where it gets
really fun is now we can go to YouTube
and we can see which video
ideas based on
these have a lot of views on them and
this is how we can come up with great
ideas to use for our lead magnets top
five strategies for walking your dog how
to set the perfect price for dog walking
and grooming services let's go to
YouTube and type that in
pricing your
grooming
services pricing your worth build your
dream clientele pet grooming cost of dog
grooming services average prices hi
America for pet and I'm a professional
pet
groom
okay let's see dog grooming cost
how to become a pet groomer how much
money do they make oh this is a good one
right here so this had a lot of those
ones only had
like 3.8 th000 views but look at this
one 415,000
views and she's got like like amazing
how to become a pet groomer hey everyone
and welcome back to my channel girl with
dogs and you got all these on the
sidebar here you can see complete dog
grooming lesson 10 things is considered
before becoming a pet
groomer okay hey guys welcome back to my
channel if you are new my name is
Savannah and today I going to tell you
and then I can go look at her Channel
and I can go under videos and I can see
the most popular video she
has uh how to build a dog stair how to
become a pet so that's a good one how
much money do they make so something
like that like how to become a pet
groomer would probably be a good video
idea
or a good lead magnet idea that you
could create right there and then you
could create even a training just like
this like she's got right
here and then that's what people can opt
in for and then the next step is to uh
either sign up with you to to work with
you and so look at this like even she
has right here learn to gromd dogs.com
okay world's largest Library a
professional so this isn't even her
business this is probably just something
that she's referring people to but if
she had her own business let's see pause
and relax so she has mobile
grooming fully booked for grooming
clientele awesome that's
great uh additional re so she's helping
people with that but she's got her own
thing she really has a great brand built
up though which is really cool so again
from there she doesn't have a next step
because she needs this training right
here but if she did have a next step for
people to take that would then lead
people to some offer that she would have
that's exactly what she would want to do
as far as that goes okay so no matter
what you're doing no matter what offer
you're doing let's go let's go check
this out right here um YouTube is just a
great resource to figure out what are
those ideas that you could create offers
around okay you can look at what are
some of the top videos on certain topics
let's look up
um
uh gut
Healing Foods okay we're going to type
this in gut Healing Foods these foods
will heal heal your gut best foods to
repair your
gut how to heal the gut
um foods to have more energy gut healing
let's say that's your Niche okay you
could just type that in right there
my current good gut health routine how I
heal and change my gut how to improve
your gut health so again these could all
be you could reverse engineer these into
lead
magnets of some kind people could sign
up for to give you their
information and you'll notice right here
check you know he's got different
sponsors stuff like that sign up for my
newsletter get my ebook 10 things every
plastic surgery patient must know okay
so again he's got lots of different
stuff because that's that's what his uh
Niche is right here younger for
life but you can go look at and that's
the other that's the other way to find
other good lead magnets is look at what
other lead magnets different people in
your space offer what different offers
do they have you could go on Facebook
and you could see if you check out a
couple of different pages if you start
searching different topics and content
they will start feeding you ads that are
related to the niche of whatever your
Market is and so go click on an
ad I do this all the time by the way
click on an ad that you see right here
and this will give you an idea as far as
what you could create an offer around
you just click on ads that are on social
media and again because I do so much
with advertising and Facebook ads it's
going to really lead me to that those
types of
offers um however
for whatever your Niche is if you start
scrolling content that's related to your
Niche you can click on different ads and
offers and see okay what are different
headlines what are different
um
um Hooks and opportunities and ideas
that people are promoting already with
their ads and you could take one of
those edit it just a little bit teach
your own version of it create a lead
magnet with that and use that to grow
your email list and so listen if you are
a coach if you are a course
and you're trying to figure this out I'd
love to work with you and help you with
that that's exactly what we do inside of
my client growth accelerator program as
we work with coaches and mentors on how
to create the best lead magnets on on
how to Market their business on how to
attract those clients to them what is
the right way to do so and I will work
personally with you by taking a look at
your offers by taking a look at your
copy your ads and Diving deep in with
you to show you okay do this don't do
that and that's what I do every single
day inside of of our coaching Community
inside of the client growth accelerator
program so again I'd love to work with
you there as well click on the link in
our description and jump in with us when
we open the doors to that or when we you
again you might it might be open now
when you find this maybe you're finding
this video a month from
now um we'd love to have you in there
we'd love to work with you inside of my
accelerator program to help you get
those results all right I'll talk soon
everybody have a good one and make sure
to subscribe to the channel as well have
a good one